and I turn back and I'm not kidding the
deer is up on its back legs like a
man it is chasing us like a man the
baby's coming it's
[Music]
[Applause]
coming w
[Music]
[Applause]
you know was podcast come to Popa please
give it up for Mr Tom Papa everybody let
him
here
this is a story about why you shouldn't
smoke pot when you're 10 years
old I was 10 years
old and I come from a large Italian
family and uh I'm one of 21
grandchildren and when I was 10 uh we
started having weddings because the
older kids were older and starting to
get married so we started to go to these
weddings which when your 10 is a pretty
kickass party up to that point you're
going to birthday parties and you're
just eating cake and you're pinning a
tail on a donkey and once you realize
everyone cheats anyway the luster comes
off and you're like it's time to move on
but you've got a ways to go before some
really good parties come and then the
weddings started kicking in we're like
this is good we're seeing grown-ups like
wasted and people are falling over and
we're seeing girlss we never saw before
these are good and we noticed that the
older kids who we wanted to hang out
with desperately would all sneak out of
the wedding with Uncle
Al at some point in the wedding they
just kind of sneak away and we never got
asked and we were bummed out cuz Uncle
Al his nickname was Uncle Al all the
kids
pal and when you're 10 you think it's
just cuz he's fun to be with but the
older kids were like no he's really your
pal and we're like all right well we
want to we want to go like how do we no
one's asking us to go what are they
doing so this wedding came and we were
like all right we got to up our game so
we wore our little 10-year-old
businessman suits me and my cousin Kenny
and we had our little Shirley temples
and we're leaning against the bar we had
combs in our pockets we were we were we
were working it and and pulling it off
totally pull just Shirley Temple in your
hand when you're 10 using the
straw and our cousins the two older
cousins we really admired were looking
at us and they started laughing and were
like oh maybe it's not going to happen
but then they approach and they're like
hey you uh you want to go outside and
see Uncle Al we're like yeah yeah we do
yeah what do we do they're like just go
out front and we'll meet you out there
and we'll take you over and we'll go see
Uncle Al we're like all right cool and
they split and we start walking and then
my aunt comes up and she's like where
you two going she straighten our little
ties we're like uh nowhere she's like
stay away from your Uncle Al he'll ruin
your
life and we're like now we really want
to
go so we walk outside and they take us
to a car and Uncle Al is sitting in the
car and they get in the car and they
don't let us in the car they roll down
the windows we lean in their little ties
hanging down and they put the window up
to like catch us like we're just stuck
in the car and Uncle Al has weed out on
his lap on a magazine I mean I'm I'm a
man now I am not 10 I am a man I have
seen weed I have I went to college I I I
used to see Dead shows I've seen weed
I'm a
man but to this day I never saw one
person have a bud that was so big as
what Uncle Al had on his lap at his
niece's
wedding and we didn't even know it was
weed he just started breaking it up we
thought they were just going to like
smoke a cigarette we didn't know that
was badass enough if you were to just
smoke anything so he rolls it up and
they start smoking it and then we're
stuck in the window they just start
blowing it in our
faces like we're a
pet if you ever get a pet high and just
blow it in their face and kind of
we were the pets in our little suits and
they just blowing it on us and we're
getting you know we're not we don't know
we're getting high we're just trying to
be cool like okay guess this is what you
do with Uncle
Al they're done they roll down the
window and we kind of fall out and they
come out and I remember it was windy and
Uncle Al is bald except for the side
hair and uh the wind is blowing and his
hair is all out like this and he just
starts going look at me I'm Bozo the
Clown I'm Bozo he just starts dancing
around
and we're like this is why everyone
loves Uncle Al he's a
clown he's
amazing so like all right you guys can't
walk in with us you guys got to go
around the back be cool we're like all
right we'll be we'll be cool and they
walk in and we walk around the back and
as soon as we walk around the back we're
lost cuz we're high and we're
10 we don't even remember there's a
wedding we have to get back to we're
just wandering in our little businessman
attire and we come around the back
there's like a golf course there and
there's these little woods you know like
little woods in New Jersey you know
probably three trees but woods and uh
there's a deer there's a deer just
sitting there eating the grass and if
you've ever been high in nature you feel
for some reason like you're one with
nature like there's a like it speaks to
you whatever it is a rock or an animal
and this deer just kind of looked at us
and we looked at the deer and then we
looked at each other and made the
decision of what two 10-year-old kids in
Jersey would decide which is we've got
to catch
it now if you're a man and you're in
your business attire you don't just run
into the woods even if it was something
great if it was a bag of money you were
like let's let's change and then we'll
go back and run into the woods but when
you're 10 you just start running in your
businessman suit and the deer took off
and went into the woods and we're in the
woods and we're laughing now now we're
start you know this is the first time
ever 10 first of all everything's funny
when you're 10 then get Uncle Al's crazy
weed on top and now you're chasing a
deer in the jungle we're just laughing
our asses off we go running in there the
deer's like running and I turned to my
cousin I'm like Kenny at what point like
if we catch it what do we do with it and
he just looks at me like crazy like in
his crazy eyes he goes we're going to
eat it
that's a disturbing thing to hear your
cousin say we don't have tools we don't
have cooking we have nothing no weapons
his idea is we're just going to start
biting it like another animal but I
couldn't even focus on that because I'm
looking I look over at the deer the deer
it's like a New Jersey deer that just
heard what we were saying and he's
stopped now and looking at us like what
did you
say
you going to eat me and he takes a step
towards us we're like laugh and we take
a step back then he takes two steps
towards us we take two more steps back
and all of a sudden there's like that
moment where you know you're under
attack and we just start but we're
laughing like remember when you were a
kid you would be so filled with joy
sometimes with laughter that your legs
physically don't work it doesn't happen
as an adult you never laugh so hard that
you can't
even so picture two little
lawyers
just we got he's picking up speed we got
to get out of here and I'm starting to
get a little further than Kenny and then
I hear Kenny let out a
scream like a hi like there's a reason
they put 10-year-old boys in the
choir because they can hit a a a a
volume and a pitch that only angels can
hit it's a it's higher than girls
it's so much higher than I can even do
it in the woods and I hear that scream
it's fear and it's just I like death and
Angelic and I'm laughing and I turn back
and I'm not kidding the deer is up on
its back legs like a
man it is chasing us like a man
I come in with my
scream our suits are little businessman
suits and this thing is just coming at
us like you're not eating
me we just got to get out of the woods
we just got to get the hell out of the
woods and we kind of make our way it's
like he could have like attacked us but
in his head like if I could read a
deer's mind which when I was that high I
kind of did he was like I'm just going
to scare these little guys these These
are the smallest businessmen I've ever
[Applause]
seen I don't even know why they're in
the woods but I'm just going to do the
back leg thing and get them out of
here so we make our way out of the woods
we're crawling we're mud covered we're
crying we're not laughing anymore we're
crying we're lost and we see up oh
there's the windows of the party of the
wedding and we come up and we're just
like so out we're like we are wrecked I
don't know what I don't I don't know I'm
high but I know this is a weird
day this is a day I'm going to remember
I don't know what they blew in our faces
but I don't want to be at a wedding I
don't want to be a
businessman I don't want to hunt deer
with my
face we see uncle alie's in there in the
middle of all the parents and he's
telling some animated sto St and they're
all looking really pissed off and he's
laughing with his Bozo hair we're like
we can't we got to sit down and get
catch our breath and we sit on these
lounge chairs we just like we are
wrecked and all of a sudden my aunt the
same Aunt comes I remember the sky was
blue and then all we're just finally
chilling out it was just peaceful for a
minute and then her face just came in
the middle of that scene and what did I
tell you your uncle's in there ruining
your
life we never got high again until uh we
were 11
thank you guys so
[Applause]
much